{
    "id": "b63ec576cf864dfcb01cc9a3c4c19518",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was deaf ………………………………. our pleas for help.",
            "description": "Deaf is followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Physical activity is beneficial …………………………… health.",
            "description": "We say beneficial to something or somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you conscious ……………………………….. your rights and responsibilities?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She refused to comply …………………………………. my request.",
            "description": "We say comply with.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The honor was conferred ………………………………. him at the convocation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He congratulated me ………………………………. my new job.",
            "description": "Congratulate can be followed by on or for.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is thoroughly conversant ……………………………… the problem.",
            "description": "Conversant is followed by with.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager called ………………………………… an explanation from the cashier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t care ……………………………… your opinion. If I want to do something, I will do it.",
            "description": "To care about something is to think that it is important. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He fell …………………………….. suspicion.",
            "description": "When you fall under something, you become affected by it. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "under",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The inspector has promised to inquire …………………………………. the complaint.",
            "description": "To inquire into is the look into or probe.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He inquired …………………………….. homes for sale.",
            "description": "To inquire about is to ask about.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "about",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}